https://www.hermys.com/privacy/

69 CENTRE STREET | PORT CLINTON, PA 19549
Open Tuesday 9am-6pm | Wednesday-Friday 9am-5pm | Saturday 9am-3pm Closed Sunday & Monday
Privacy
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Pixel Motion and Hermy's BMW / Triumph. Pixel Motion and Hermy's BMW / Triumph promote the use of fair information practices. Because Pixel Motion and Hermy's BMW / Triumph are committed to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE:
Pixel Motion is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. Pixel Motion and Hermy's BMW / Triumph will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Pixel Motion and Hermy's BMW / Triumph collect information from our users at several different points on the web site.
VEHICLE QUOTE REQUESTS:
In order to obtain a vehicle price quote, a user must first complete a Quote Request Form. A user is required to give their contact information (such as name, address, telephone number and e-mail address). This information is used to contact the user and provide the quote or other information that they have requested. It is optional for the user to provide financial information, but can be done so that Hermy's BMW / Triumph can review and pre-qualify the user for financing if they are interested. All customer information obtained via the quote request form is encrypted for security purposes and stored on a secured server.
ORDERS:
Information is requested from the user on the e-Catalog order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If Hermy's BMW / Triumph has trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. All customer information obtained via the order form is encrypted for security purposes and stored on a secured server.
COOKIES:
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For example, a cookie is used to store items during e-Catalog shopping so that a list of what you are ordering is maintained. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use the site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user, may not be able to use the e-Catalog shopping basket function on the site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on the site.
LOG FILES:
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic and geographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
SHARING:
We may share demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is generally not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. However, Pixel Motion and/or Hermy's BMW / Triumph may send E-mails or mail about special offers at the Dealership or other offers or information that may be of interest to the user based on the information we collect. Hermy's BMW / Triumph uses an outside company (such as UPS, USPS, Fed Ex. etc.) to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not to our knowledge, retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
LINKS:
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Pixel Motion and Hermy's BMW / Triumph are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
SURVEY AND CONTESTS:
From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or may offer contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code and age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES:
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
SECURITY:
This web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.
When our quote request or order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just “surfing”.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, has restricted access at Pixel Motion and at the dealership. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, order clerk, sales representative, or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Access to the information is made via a password-protected site. Each time an employee needs to access information, they must enter their password to gain access to the information. Furthermore, employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Employees are periodically notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected.
SUPPLEMENTATION OF INFORMATION:
In order for this web site to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it may be necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources.
For example, to determine if customers qualify for financing, the dealership may use their name and social security number to request a credit report or approval from a lending institution.
SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES:
Pixel Motion and Hermy's BMW / Triumph may send the user site and service announcement updates which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regard to issues relating to their account via e-mail or phone.
CORRECTING / UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION:
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as address or E-mail), or if a user no longer desires to receive information from Pixel Motion and Hermy's BMW / Triumph, we will endeavor to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data from our database.
Contacting the Web Sites
If you have questions concerning this Privacy Policy or the practices of these sites, you may contact us.
Additional information regarding Pixel Motion Privacy Policy can be found here.
All New InventoryUsed InventoryFinancingSchedule ServiceSalesSales Department HoursMonday: ClosedTuesday: 9:00AM - 6:00PMWednesday: 9:00AM - 5:00PMThursday: 9:00AM - 5:00PMFriday: 9:00AM - 5:00PMSaturday: 9:00AM - 3:00PMSunday: Closed
©2020. Hermy's BMW / Triumph. All Rights Reserved.
Directions
Privacy
Terms
Contact Us
Sitemap
Triumph BMW
Click to call sales
While great effort is made to ensure the accuracy of the information on this site, errors can occur.
Please verify all pricing information with a customer service representative.
This is easily done by calling us or visiting us at the dealership.
My Vehicles
Listed below are your saved and recently viewed vehicles
CLOSE X
My Saved Vehicles ()
My Recently Viewed Vehicles ()
Compare
Vehicles
|
Logout
You can also view your saved vehicles on other devices.
Sign up
Sign In
Save your vehicles.
Have your vehicles with you
Save your favorite vehicles for later viewing on your desktop or mobile devices.
Recently Viewed Vehicles
Keep track of all the vehicles you've viewed for a better car shopping experience.
Compare saved vehicles
Narrow your search by comparing your favorite vehicles.
Log in to view your saved vehicles.
Enter your email
Sign Up
Sign In
Already registered? Sign in.
Or sign up to access your saved vehicles and
recently viewed vehicles on all your devices.
Vehicle Comparison
CLOSE
Condition
Price
Year
Make
Model
Trim
Select total out of pocket
$0 out of pocket$1 to $500 out of pocket$501 to $1,000 out of pocket$1,001 to $1,500 out of pocket$1,501 to $2,000 out of pocket$2,001 to $2,500 out of pocket$2,501 to $3,000 out of pocketOver $3,001 out of pocket
Select Your Mileage
10,000 mi. / yr
12,000 mi. / yr
15,000 mi. / yr
First Name
Last Name
Phone
Message
Zip Code*Message
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Start My Purchase
×
Schedule Service
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeMakeModelDate
Date Format: MM slash DD slash YYYY
Date entered above will be confirmed by a service advisor.What service do you need?
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Order Parts
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeWhat parts are you looking for?
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Value Your Trade
What vehicle are you interested in?
Filling out this section helps us evaluate the purchase of the new/used bike, and trade-in potential values of your current bike.
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeWhat vehicle are you trading in?
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Make an Offer
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeMessage
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Check Availability
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeMessage
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Special Offers
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeMessage
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Commercial Request
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip Code
New (709)
Ram (262)
Model
Ram 1500
Ram 2500
Ram 3500
Ram ProMaster 2500
Ram ProMaster 3500
Ram ProMaster 1500
Ram ProMaster City
Year
2016
2017
Message
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Contact Us
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip Code*Message
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
Models BMW
Triumph
AdventureHeritageRoadsterSportTourUrban Mobility20212021 K 1600 Grand America2019C 400 X2020C 650 GT2019C 650 GT2018C Evolution2021F 750 GS2021F 750 GS2020F 750 GS2020F 850 GS2021F 850 GS2021F 850 GS2020F 850 GS Adventure2021F 850 GS Adventure2021 F 850 GS Adventure2021F 900 R2020F 900 R2020F 900 XR2021F 900 XR2020G 310 GS2019G 310 GS2019G 310 R2020G 310 R2019K 1600 B2020K 1600 B2021K 1600 B2020K 1600 Grand America2019K 1600 Grand America2020K 1600 GT2019K 1600 GT2021K 1600 GTL2019K 1600 GTL2020K 1600 GTL2021M 1000 RR2019R 1250 GS2021R 1250 GS2021R 1250 GS2021R 1250 GS2020R 1250 GS2020R 1250 GS Adventure2021R 1250 GS Adventure2020R 1250 R2021R 1250 RS2020R 1250 RS2020R 1250 RT2021R 182021R 18 Classic2019R nineT2020R nineT2020R nineT /52020R nineT Pure2020R nineT Scrambler2021S 1000 R2020S 1000 R2020S 1000 RR2020S 1000 XR2021S 1000 XR2021S1000 RRAdventure FamilyBonneville FamilyTriple Family20201200 Range2020Adventure 9002020Bobber Black2020BOBBER TFC2020Bonneville BobberBonneville Bobber TFC2020Bonneville Speedmaster2020Bonneville T100Bonneville T100 BlackBonneville T100 Bud Ekins2020Bonneville T120Bonneville T120 AceBonneville T120 BlackBonneville T120 Bud EkinsBonneville T120 Diamond2020DAYTONA MOTO 2
Limited Edition2020Rocket 32020Rocket 3 GTRocket 3 R2020Rocket 3 TFC2020Scrambler 1200Scrambler 1200 XC Scrambler 1200 XE2020Speed Triple2020Speed Twin2020Street Scrambler2020Street Triple2020Street Twin2020Thruxton 1200 Range2020Thruxton RS2020Thruxton TFCTiger 900 GTTiger 900 GT LOWTiger 900 GT ProTiger 900 Pure WhiteTiger 900 Rally2020Tiger 900 Rally ProTriple R Low
CLOSE
A TRUCKLOAD OF ADRENALINE IS HEADED OUR WAY
Friday 8 AM to 4:30 PM and Saturday 8 AM to 4:30 PM
We’re excited to announce that the BMW Demo Truck, loaded with all the latest BMW motorcycles, will be set up in our parking lot for 2 days — and we’ve put together an incredible weekend of events to celebrate with our customers. Sales, service and parts will be open during the event with safety guidelines in place. So we can all be together — just not too close.
Schedule a demo ride and feel the adrenaline rush through your body as you roll on the throttle and immerse yourself in the awe-inspiring, dynamics of BMW Motorrad. Not sure which BMW is right for you? This is your chance to speak with a BMW expert who can help guide you to the BMW that matches your personal riding style.
Check out our current inventory of new and used bikes. Our sales staff will be on hand to answer your questions and inform you of all the latest BMW programs available. We also have a wide selection of BMW Riding Gear and Lifestyle Apparel to get you outfitted to Make Life a Ride!
Want to get one step closer to riding the BMW Motorcycle of your dreams at Hermys BMW. Preregister here: hermysbmw.bmwmotorcyclesevents.com
Demo Ride Signup starts at 8:00 AM each Day of the Event
Authentic Texas Cuisine on Saturday at 11:30 with Backwoods Brothers – Individually prepared and wrapped pulled chicken and pork sandwiches with sides of cole slaw or pasta Salad – Drinks
Storewide Customer Appreciation Sale Friday and Saturday
*Hermy’s is required to follow Pennsylvania State and Federal CDC guidelines for protective mask use while inside the showroom, parts and accessory areas and any outdoor areas where social distancing is not possible, thank you.
40 YEARS OF GS bike show and FARKLE FEST.
Saturday, September 26, 2020 at 9 AM – 3 PM
During our demo day we will be celebrating the GS. We invite you to bring out your GS/GSA and show it off. We will have hand made trophies for each class. Most miles on a gs/gsa, most farkles, farthest distance to arrive and dirtiest gs/gsa. If you don’t know what farkles are you need some! We will have the BMW demo truck set up if you would like to ride anything in their line up. Food at 11:30 registration for the show opens at 9 AM trophies awarded at 1pm.
40 Years of GS RIDE.
Sunday, September 27, 2020 at 9 AM – 1 PM
Join us for a beginner friendly 40 Years of GS RIDE. It will be on dirt road/back roads leaving from Hermy’s at 9:20 AM and arriving back at Hermy’s around 1 PM. This ride can be completed without knobby tires depending on your abilities. But if you have them it will make it easier for you. Make sure to bring water and a snack. All makes and models welcome! Contact Bobby Brown for any information you need. 610.562.7303 Ext: 21 or bobby.brown@hermys.com
CLOSE
×
